export const questions = [
  {
    question: 'How is the corona virus spread?',
    answer: 'Person to person',
    explanation:
      'Covid19 is transmitted through Person to Person conflict',
    false_answers: ['Airbourne', 'Waterbourne', 'Bloodbourne']
  },
  {
    question: 'How did the corona virus start?',
    answer: 'Wet Market in Wuhan',
    explanation:
      'Sources say that the virus came from a "Wet Market" in Wuhan which sold both dead and live animals',
    false_answers: [
      'Okavango Delta National Park, Africa',
      'Lake Natron, Africa',
      'Darien Gap - Colombia'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country has been effected most?',
    answer: 'USA',
    explanation:
      '"In the United States, at least 81,321 people are known to have been infected with the coronavirus, including more than 1,000 deaths â€” more cases than China, Italy or any other country has seen, according to data gathered by The New York Times." - Donald G. Mcneil Jr',
    false_answers: ['China', 'Canada', 'Africa']
  },
  {
    question:
      'What should you **NOT** do in order to prevent yourself from getting Covid19?',
    answer: 'Not take the precautions from governments and hospitals seriously',
    explanation:
      'Between people who are in close contact with one another (within about 6 feet).',
    false_answers: [
      'Hang with friends',
      'Go to a bar',
      'Dont listen to what the government and hospitals'
    ]
  },
  {
    question:
      'How long Should you self isolate if you think you contain the virus?',
    answer: '14 days',
    explanation:
      'stay at home and monitor yourself for symptoms, even if mild, for 14 days',
    false_answers: ['1 day', '5 days', '10 days']
  },
  {
    question: 'Which groups are most at risk?',
    answer: 'Elderly and people with asthma or weak immune systems',
    explanation:
      'Older adults and people of any age who have serious underlying medical conditions, like asthma, may be at higher risk for more serious complications from COVID-19.',
    false_answers: ['Millennials', 'Children', 'Middle Aged People']
  },
  {
    question: 'What has the corona virus effected',
    answer: 'All answers',
    explanation: 'Economies in every countries have been falling at a tremendous pace, Buisnesses getting forced to shut down, Schools closing, and the Trade collapsing',
    false_answers: ['Buisnesses', 'Schools', 'Trade']
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the signs and symptoms?',
    answer: 'Fever, Cough, Shortness of breath',
    explanation: 'Fever, Cough, Shortness of breath are symptoms and signs of Covid19',
    false_answers: [
        "Running Nose",
        "Sleepy",
        "Depression"
    ]
  },{
    question: 'Which one of these people can spread the virus?',
    answer: 'People who currently have the virus',
    explanation: 'People infected are the people who can spread the virus, not people who have been through quarantine or have been released from isolation',
    false_answers: [
        "People who have came out of isolation",
        "People who have had the virus previously and have recovered",
        "People who don't have the virus"
    ]
  },{
    question: 'What ethnicities get effected the most',
    answer: 'Person of any ethnicity or race',
    explanation: 'Person of any ethnicity or race can get the virus, all should follow precautions set by the government and health care facilities',
    false_answers: [
        "Asians",
        "Whites",
        "African's"
    ]
  }
];
